Close Close

* PRODUCTS
* COMPANY
* SUPPORT

* [中文 (Chinese)](https://www.marvell.com/content/marvell-com/zh.html "中文 (Chinese)")
* [日本語 (Japanese)](https://www.marvell.com/content/marvell-com/ja.html "日本語 (Japanese)")

* PRODUCTS
* COMPANY
* SUPPORT

English

* PRODUCTS

* BY TYPE
* BY MARKET

#### Compute

#### Networking

#### Storage

#### Custom

#### [Carrier](https://www.marvell.com/solutions/carrier.html)

#### [Automotive](https://www.marvell.com/solutions/automotive.html)

#### [Data Center & Cloud](https://www.marvell.com/solutions/data-center.html)

#### [Enterprise](https://www.marvell.com/solutions/enterprise.html)

* COMPANY

#### Our Company

#### Media

#### Contact

* SUPPORT

#### Support by Product

#### Tools & Resources

BY TYPE

Compute

Networking

Storage

Custom

BY MARKET

[Watch the latest

**Marvell Essential Technology Videos**

WATCH NOW](https://videos.marvell.com/)

Our Company

Media

Contact

[Watch the latest

**Marvell Essential Technology Videos**

WATCH NOW](https://videos.marvell.com/)

Support by Product

Tools & Resources

Privacy Statement
=================

1. Privacy Statement 

Marvell Website Privacy Statement
=================================

January, 2020  

In this Marvell Website Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement"), Marvell Technology, Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries ("Marvell", "we", "us", our") describes the collection, use, sharing and other processing of information and data ("Personal Data") pertaining to individual users ("you", "your") of all Marvell websites including [http://marvell.com](http://marvell.com/) and all associated sub-domains (the "Sites") and your rights and choices regarding our processing of such Personal Data.  If you are a resident of a country subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), please refer to the EEA Supplemental Privacy Statement.

**1. Processing Activities Covered**

This Privacy Statement applies to the collection of Personal Data on the Sites and its subsequent use in the context, particularly, of the following activities:

* your registration of a user account on the Sites (e.g., "Marvell Extranet"),
* your signing up for newsletters on the Sites (e.g., "Smart Connections"),
* your registration for an event or webinar through the Sites,
* your provision of Personal Data to us by entering information in any other data entry fields or web form embedded in the Sites (e.g., "Request for Information),
* your download of content made available via the Sites,
* the collection and analysis of Personal Data regarding your use of the Sites, and
* communications between you and us based on your interaction with the Sites.

Links to third-party websites on the Site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Site. Marvell has not reviewed all of these third-party websites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these websites, their content or their privacy policies. Thus, Marvell does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third-party websites linked on this Site, you do this entirely at your own risk.

**2. What Personal Data Do We Collect?**  

The Personal Data that we collect from or about you may particularly include the following:

* If you express an interest in obtaining additional information about our services, request customer support, use our "Contact Us" or similar features, register for a user account on the Site, sign up for a newsletter, an event or a webinar, or download certain content, we generally require you to provide us with your contact information, such as your name, job title, company name, address, phone number, email address, or username and password;
* If you use and interact with the Site, we automatically collect log files and other information about your device and your usage of the Site through cookies, web beacons or similar technologies, such as IP-addresses or other identifiers (see Section 5 below).

**3\. Purposes Underlying the Processing of Your Personal Data**  

We collect and otherwise process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

* Operating the Site: We process your Personal Data to the extent this is necessary to operate and administer the Site and to provide you with content you access and request (e.g., download of certain content from the Site);
* Promoting security of the Site: We process your Personal Data by monitoring your use of the Site, verifying accounts, and by investigating suspicious activity as well as violations of our terms and policies in order to promote the safety and security of the systems and applications used for the Site and to protect the rights and property of others or our own rights and interests;
* Managing user registrations: We process your Personal Data to administer your user account established on the Site (if any);
* Handling contact and user support requests: If you fill out a “Contact Me” web form, request customer or user support, or if you contact us by other means through the Site, we process your Personal Data in order to respond to your request and communicate with you;
* Managing event registrations and attendance: Where applicable, we process your Personal Data to plan and host events or webinars that you have registered for on the Site;
* Developing and improving the Site: We may process your Personal Data to analyze trends and track your usage of the Site in order to further develop and improve the Site and provide our users with a more pleasant online experience;  
* Displaying personalized advertisements and content: We may process your Personal Data to conduct marketing research, advertise to you, or provide personalized information and content to you based upon your activities and interests displayed on the Site;
* Sending marketing communications: Subject to the applicable legal requirements, we may process your Personal Data to send you marketing information, product recommendations, information about our promotions or events, and other non‑transactional communications about us and our affiliates and partners via email, SMS, push notification or other means of communication;
* Complying with legal obligations: We may process your Personal Data in accordance with our legal obligations under the applicable law or to the extent necessary to protect our rights, pursue remedies available to us or to respond to lawful requests.

**4\. Who Do We Share Your Personal Data With?**  

We may share the Personal Data you provide, or parts thereof, with the following recipients:

* third-party vendors or other Marvell entities processing your Personal Data on our behalf to provide services such as IT operation and administration, customer support, or marketing and analytics;
* other Marvell entities involved in the management of your customer account (if any) or providing information necessary to respond to a request you have submitted via the Site;
* third parties or other Marvell entities organizing, hosting or sponsoring an event or webinar you may have registered for on the Site;
* third parties contemplating a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or other business transaction involving Marvell in which the third party will assume control of all or part of Marvell’s business;
* third-party professional advisors such as attorneys, auditors and insurers (where necessary to provide their services).

**5\. Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies**  

We use cookies on our website.  You can control whether some of the cookies are set via the Preferences Manager.  For additional information about cookies, including the types and specific cookies used on our website, please access the Preferences Manager. You may also be able to restrict the use of web beacons and other identifiers through a “privacy” or similar section in the tool bar of your browser window.

Click here to view/modify Cookie Settings

**6\. Changes to This Privacy Statement**  

We will update this Privacy Statement from time to time by posting an updated version on the Site to reflect changes in our practices, technology, legal requirements or other factors. If we do, we will update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Statement.

We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to stay informed about our collection, processing and sharing of your Personal Data.

**7\. Contacting Us**  

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement or our data processing operations, you can use the following contact details to address them with us: [Privacy@marvell.com](mailto:Privacy@marvell.com).

EEA Supplemental Website Privacy Statement
==========================================

Marvell provides to users located in the European Economic Area (EEA) this Supplemental Privacy Statement ("Supplemental Statement"), which contains additional information for such users to supplement the above Privacy Statement. If you are not located in the European Economic Area, this Supplemental Statement does not apply to you.

**1\. Controller**  

Marvell Technology, Inc., 5488 Marvell Lane, Santa Clara, CA 95054, United States is the controller responsible for the collection and subsequent processing of your Personal Data on or through the Site as described in the Privacy Statement and this Supplemental Statement, unless expressly specified otherwise.

You may contact us by sending an email to Privacy@marvell.com.

**2\. Legal Bases for the Processing of Your Personal Data**  

Our processing of your Personal Data relies on the following legal bases:

* Based on the necessity to enter into or perform a contract with you:  To the extent that we enter into a contract with you in the context of your use of the Site (governing terms and conditions), your completion of a user registration, your request for customer or user support, your registration or attendance of events or webinars, or your use of similar functionalities of the Site, our related processing of your Personal Data is based on the necessity to enter into or perform such contract;
* Based on legitimate interests: Unless we enter into a related contract with you, our processing of your Personal Data in the context of the following activities is based on the necessity to pursue our legitimate interests to

Ø  administer the Site and provide you with content you access and request (e.g., information posted on the Site, download of content from the Site, etc.);

Ø  promote the safety and security of the Site, our IT connected to the Site and the users of the Site;

Ø  respond to requests you make when filling out a “Contact Me” web form, seeking customer or user support, or contacting us by other means through the Site;

Ø  administer your registration and attendance of an event or webinar;

Ø  comply with legal obligations under the law of jurisdictions outside of the European Union;

Ø  develop and improve the Site or display personalized advertisements or other personalized content. Detailed information about the analytics and advertising solutions used for these purposes can be found in Section 3 below;

Ø  send you marketing communications as described in Section 3 of the Privacy Statement via email\].  You will be offered the option to opt out of further marketing communications in the context of each marketing communication you receive from us.

* Based on compliance with legal obligations: To the extent we are subject to legal obligations under the law of the EU or an EU Member State, we may process your Personal Data to comply with relevant laws, regulatory requirements and to respond to lawful requests, court orders, and legal process.

**3\. Cookies, Analytics and Advertising Solutions**  

We use cookies on our website.  You can control whether some of the cookies are set via the Preferences Manager.  For additional information about cookies, including the types and specific cookies used on our website, please access the Preferences Manager. You may also be able to restrict the use of web beacons and other identifiers through a “privacy” or similar section in the tool bar of your browser window.

Click here to view/modify Cookie Settings

**4\. Data Recipients in Third Countries**  

We and many of our affiliated entities and third-party service providers are located in the United States or other jurisdictions outside of the EU/EEA that are not subject to an unqualified adequacy decision by the EU Commission finding them to provide a level of protection of fundamental rights and freedoms that is essentially equivalent to that guaranteed within the EU.

However, to ensure an appropriate level of protection of your Personal Data, we enter into data processing and data transfer agreements with our affiliated entities and third-party service providers outside of the EU/EEA that incorporate the provisions of the Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the EU Commission or implement other appropriate safeguards with them. 

**5\. Data Retention**  

We implement appropriate retention periods for your Personal Data collected or otherwise processed on or through the Site. Personal Data processed in the context of a contract with you will be retained by us for the term of the contract and for a reasonable time afterwards as might be required to determine and settle any related claims. Where our processing of your personal data is based on legitimate interests or the compliance with legal obligations, it will be deleted as soon as the underlying purpose has expired. Personal data processed based on your consent will be deleted if and when you withdraw such consent.

**6\. Your Rights Relating to Your Personal Data**  

Depending on the circumstances and subject to the conditions set out in the applicable law, you have, without limitation, the right to do the following in connection with our processing of your Personal Data:

* Request access to your Personal Data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to inquire whether and what kind of Personal Data we hold about you and how it is processed, and to request a copy of such Personal Data, provided always that this does not adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others;
* Request correction and supplementation of the Personal Data that we hold about you that is incorrect, incomplete or out-of-date in light of the purposes underlying the processing;
* Request the erasure of your Personal Data where it is no longer necessary for the purposes underlying the processing, processed based on withdrawn consent, processed for legitimate interests that, in the context of your objection (see below), do not prove to be compelling, or processed in non-compliance with applicable legal requirements;
* Object to our processing of your Personal Data based on our legitimate interests where there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to our use on this ground;
* Where applicable, withdraw your consent to our processing of your Personal Data with future effect. Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer use your Personal Data for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so in law;
* Request the restriction of our processing of your Personal Data in certain situations where you feel its processing is inappropriate. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your Personal Data, for example, if you want us to establish its accuracy; and
* To the extent technically feasible, request portability of Personal Data you have provided to us, where the processing of such Personal Data is based on consent or a contract with you and is carried out by automated means.

You may enforce your rights (as may be applicable) by contacting us via the contact details stated in Section 1 of the Privacy Statement.

We are committed to working with you to address any privacy concern.  However, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent supervisory authority.

**7\. Your Provision of Personal Data to Us**  

Your use of the Site and your provision of Personal Data to us in the process is purely voluntary on your part. Subject to your sole discretion, you can, at any point, cease use of the Site or, where applicable, opt out of certain data processing operations while using the site as described in this Supplemental Statement. An exception applies if and to the extent that you want to enter into or perform a contract with us on or through the Site. In this event, providing us with your related Personal Data is a condition to our ability to enter into the contract with you or provide any contractual services to you.

Copyright © 2021 Marvell.  All rights reserved.

##### Company

##### Support

##### Careers

##### Worldwide

* Copyright © 2024 Marvell, All rights reserved.
